{
    "list":[
        {"Question":"telehone","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"hairDryer","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"shampoo","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"kettle","Answer":"metal","Wrong":"plastic"},
        {"Question":"magazine","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"plastic"},
        {"Question":"pictureBook","Answer":"paper","Wrong":"plastic"},
        {"Question":"vase","Answer":"glass","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"toothpaste","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"toothbrush","Answer":"plastic","Wrong":"paper"},
        {"Question":"tunacan","Answer":"metal","Wrong":"paper"}
    ],
    "dic":{
        "telehone":["plastic","paper"],
        "hairDryer":["plastic","paper"],
        "shampoo":["plastic","paper"],
        "kettle":["metal","plastic"],
        "magazine":["plastic","plastic"],
        "pictureBook":["paper","plastic"],
        "vase":["glass","paper"],
        "toothpaste":["plastic","paper"],
        "toothbrush":["plastic","paper"],
        "tunacan":["metal","paper"]
    }
}
